Brother Wu Ming
It's time for your shot.
I was healing Ayi's heart meridian
and passed out from depleted essence.
I should be at the Dao Medicine Hall.
Why am I here?
Is this...
a dream?
No, wait.
This feels way too real.
Could it be Ancestral Master
summoning me back to answer for my sins?
Ancestral Master, forgive me!
Your disciple shall break this dream at once.
I'll kowtow and atone upon my return.
Spirit illuminates the Purple Palace.
Wisdom's blade cuts through the void.
One thought turns the light inward.
My mind is clear and bright.
Break the dream!
Cast out desires and the heart grows still,
clear the mind and the spirit turns pure.
By decree of the Jade Pure One,
shatter illusion, return to truth!
So this isn't a dream?
An...
Ancestor Master!
You...
I've long wanted to see
just what you, you insolent disciple,
actually look like.
Treating my tomb like your own backyard,
taking my essence blood every other day.
Ancestor Master, your essence blood
is truly a peerless, priceless elixir.
But your humble disciple
only used it to save lives, you know?
My reverence for you, Ancestor Master,
flows endlessly,
like a mighty river without end.
Saving lives?
Then why move my true body
out of my tomb at will,
placing me in the mortal world?
Worse still,
sticking needles all over my true body,
acting in defiance of all decency,
desecrating my person!
She knows everything.
That was to perfect my needle technique,
to heal the world.
No disrespect was ever intended.
And there was that one time...
You...
You dared press your head against my chest!
Such behavior,
how is it any different from a lecher?
I'm wronged, Ancestor Master!
I've never done such a thing!
I refuse to admit it.
It must be that
you've slumbered too long, Ancestor Master,
and your dreams are confused.
From start to finish,
have you ever truly revered me?
Of course I have!
Ancestor Master,
let go first.
I can't breathe.
Please, let go first.
Insolent disciple!
Stop this at once!
You stop and I'll stop.
Am I beautiful?
Ancestor Master.
Beautiful.
You're the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
Do you mean that?
Absolutely, every word.
Just you wait. I'll come for you.
You're dead meat.
When did this nuisance wake up?
I'm done for, done for, done for!
Caught red-handed again.
What are you doing?
Hubby, you're awake!
They've all been so worried about you.
I'll go tell them right now.
Who did this?
Huizi put that on you.
She said your neck was injured,
so this is to keep it stable.
Right,
to keep it stable.
Get out.
You got it!
Oh, by the way,
Hubby, you've got such a great body.
Let's play again next time, okay?
Why do I feel so drained all over?
My kidney essence is depleted this badly?
Did I get robbed by bandits or what?
The women in this place...
are absolutely terrifying.
Some are bone dry from drought,
while others are drowning in floods.
Ming, your threshold got trampled today.
These women,
usually so cold and unapproachable.
But today,
they all turned into bandits.
Why didn't they assault me too?
What do you mean, assault?
You know...
what does it feel like?
Your brow is dark with bad omens.
You're in for terrible luck.
Are you kidding me?
I've got you.
What kind of bad luck could I have?
You...
What did you do to me?
You didn't guard the door when I was out!
You let my kidney essence get drained dry.
You won't get off easy either.
Ming,
why do I feel like
I'm completely out of energy,
and have lost all desire for love?
Now that's more like it.
Got any grilled kidneys?
Let's grill some!
Good thing I'm faking unconsciousness.
He must've seen everything.
No,
I really am unconscious.
I don't know a thing.
I can't let him see anything's wrong.
This might be a bit uncomfortable.
Bear with it.
Bear with it, my foot!
I'm unconscious, I don't know anything!
I'm going crazy.
This is awful.
He must know I'm not unconscious.
I've always wondered,
you insolent disciple,
what you actually look like.
Treating my tomb like your own backyard,
taking my essence blood every other day.
Just you wait. I'll come for you.
You're dead meat.
Why do I feel a chill down my spine?
Ayi,
focus your mind and listen carefully.
This is the Three Turns of Clear Vision.
It cultivates the eyes,
piercing through all illusions.
Your heart meridian has just healed,
your spirit essence not yet stable.
As the gold needle guides the medicine,
it's the perfect time to impart this art.
Follow my incantation:
Look inward to find the path,
sense the vital energy without.
Clear vision shines upon all things.
From this day forward,
this is your new life.
These eyes will reveal the world's colors,
and see through all lies and illusions.
Use them well,
Ayi.